在提供的示例代码里，你会注意到，
In the sample code provided you'll notice
我们创建了一个HTTP URL连接。
that we create a Http Url connection. To
使用http协议在网络上发送和接受数据，
use Http to send and receive data over
我们有两端连在android。
the network, we have two clients on Android.
一个是Http Url连接类，还有一个是拼凑的Http Client类。
The Http Url connection class, as well as
这两种方式都支持Https，
the patchy Http Client class. Both options support
支持以数据流的形式上传和下载，支持配置超时，
Https, streaming uploads and downloads, configurable time outs,
支持IPB 6 和连接池。
IPB 6 and connection pooling. We recommend the
我们更推荐使用Http Url连接类，因为它更为通用，轻量级，
Http Url Connection class because it's general purpose and light
在经过优化之后，能够满足大多数Android应用程序的需求。
weight, and it's been optimized to suit the needs of
想要了解更多的网络连接知识，
most Android apps. To learn more about connecting to the
请参阅读下方的培训指南和博文链接。
network, see the training guide and blog post link below.